### **Regil Austin Diaz**

778 926 6343 | regil.diaz12@gmail.com | British Columbia

### **Summary**

Marketing major with experience in social media marketing, auditing, and people management. With strong organizational skills that leads and influences a safe and productive work environment. Always willing to learn and have a growth mindset.

#### **Skills**

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Canva, Microsoft 365 (Excel, Word, Powerpoint), Basic HTML

#### **Experience**

# UR&R Corporation | Catarman Northern Samar, Philippines Assistant Manager | 09/2019 - Present

- Managed and processed confidential documents with precision and discretion.
- Oversaw purchasing and sales of products.
- Responsible for conducting bank-to-bank transfers, and issuing checks and cash.
- Managed payroll for a workforce of more than 40 employees.

# RUD Shell Service Station | Catarman Northern Samar, Philippines Auditor | 09/2019 - Present

- Supervised in making customer billings for the company.
- In charge of checking over 30 billing accounts between three different stations to be billed to the customer.
- Responsible for compiling and organizing customer billings and company billings.
- · Guided new office staff on how to work on billing statements of customers.

# MCA Music Inc. (Universal Music Philippines) | Pasig, Metro Manila On the Job Trainee | 06/2018 - 07/2018

- · Responsible for creating social media marketing collateral for local music artists.
- Assisted in reaching out to influencers to collaborate with on promoting new song releases of local music artists.
- Conducted research to identify pertinent information for the development of effective marketing strategies.
- Assisted in doing office tasks around the office.

### **Education**

### De La Salle University | Manila, Metro Manila Bachelor of Science in Marketing Management | 02/2019

Organizations joined;

Young Entrepreneurs Society (YES)

- Assistant Vice President for Linkages AY 2016-2017
  - Initiated partnerships with other organizations in and outside of school.
  - Spearheaded a seminar called Campus Swap with Enderun Entrepreneurs Society (EES). Had 25 participants between EES and YES.
  - Assisted in handling seminars that are related to Entrepreneurship.
- Assistant Vice President for Communications AY 2017-2018
  - In charge of communicating information to both members and officers of the organizations.
  - Composed copies of social media posts for the organization.

#### **Certificates**

Shell Service Initiative for Team Excellence training (2017), Basic Occupational Safety and Health training (2019)